(Penny:)for any surprises
that might happen tomorrow.
(Amy:)What surprises?
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Bernadette:)We don't want to
spoil anything,
(Bernadette:)but you should know that Sheldon
said he's ready to be physical.
You shut your damn mouth!
(Amy:)You actually heard him say this?
(Penny:)Yes. He said he wants
to do something
(Penny:)to show you how much
you mean to him.
(exhales)
I-I can't believe it. I...
(Amy:)I don't know what to say.
(Bernadette:)Well, we're really
happy for you,
(Bernadette:)and we know how
much he cares...
I do know what to say!
Let's get me waxed!
(whirring)
(Arthur:)Why isn't it ever
Angie Dickinson's bedroom?
(Sheldon:)You're back.
It-it doesn't seem
like it's up to me.